girls don't understand they don't
understand because I'm on my eighth tour
of Grinders so girls just don't get it
they have no they're like you should do
hinge I looked at my girlfriend's phone
she was talking to some guy on hinge it
is gays it is wild the kind of screening
process women have to get through and
the questions they have to ask men to
make sure they're not [__] crazy my
friend Lily asked the guy do you have
friends
you you have fingerprints do you have I
mean it's like my screening process if
I'm talking to you and you use good
grammar I will [__] you
oh if you know how to use a semicolon
get in this colon I
I don't have that kind of confidence a
semicolon
I do feel bad for women you guys have to
go through so much I read this article
it was on BuzzFeed so it's not real but
um
not a real article but it was like 25
things women need to do to protect
themselves and it was I mean the friends
like don't be alone at night don't walk
in the same sidewalk as a man don't be
alone in a park don't look at a man
directly in the eye and as I'm going
down I'm like everything that women do
to protect themselves from men are all
things that gay men do to find other men
be alone at night in a park
stare at him directly in the eye
and that's the thing I try and explain
to straight people is that gay people we
have a power we can talk to gay men from
across the room with just looks
full-blown conversations I don't mean
small talk I mean look at you're with
your friends you're at a gay bar you
walk in it's super crazy right and you
see this guy and you're like oh my God
there's this really hot guy over there
I'm gonna go in for the first look okay
all right okay
oh
all right he looks back
I'm gonna go in for the second look okay
[Laughter]
he's in med school
we're gonna [__] I'll be back in 10 you
guys just
[Applause]
[Laughter]